片名: 堕落天使
翻译: Fledgling Taiwan
本字幕仅供 教学交流用,请勿使用于商业牟利
在有光之前  天上住着许多天使
Before there was light there were angels.
一阵黑暗后
One moment darkness
天堂又再明亮 并且充满着高贵的生命
the next heaven was bright with glorious beings.
那是多么的完美的地方
It was perfect.
但是 它没有持续很长
It did not last long.
大天使 路西法 背叛了上帝
Lucifer revolted against God.
天堂被划了一条线
A line was drawn in paradise.
战争随之开始
A war began.
每个天使 都被迫要选择
Every angel was forced to choose
选择 圣洁天堂 或是 外面混乱的世界
the holiness of heaven or the chaos that roiled outside.
有一个天使拒绝了 选择
One angel refused
他相信唯一值得征战的
believing the only thing worth fighting for
是我们现在所称的 爱情的力量
was a force we now call love.
他被逐出天堂
Cast out of heaven
但是 他不是唯一坠落人间的天使
this angel did not fall alone.
所有还没 做出选择的天使
very angel who had yet to choose
带着巨大恐惧 也坠落人间
fell in a flash of almighty fury.
这些就是坠落天使
These are the Fallen.
他们被驱逐出天堂
Exiled from heaven
他们徘回在人间
they wander the earth
被放逐,直到 那个叛逆天使(本片中的 丹尼尔)
banished until the rebel angel
放弃爱情,选择 Lucifer或是 上帝
abandons love and takes a side.
那是当时
That was then.
这是现在
This is now.
[A good start, ACADEMY OF SWORD & CROSS]
小册子介绍 [剑与十字学院]
是那里吗?
Is that it?
一定是
Must be.
[ACADEMY SWORD & CROSS]
剑与十字学院
爱你
Love you.
我的宝贝
My baby.
我真希望 我知道 如何帮助你
I just wish I knew how to help you.
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
这是小礼物
OK. It's small gift.
我要你在生日的时候 再打开
I wanted you to have something to open on your birthday.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我爱你
I love you.
再见,爸
Bye, Dad.
[FOUNDER COLIN HENRY BANCROE]
创办人 COLIN HENRY
欢迎来到 剑与十字 学院
Welcome to Sword and Cross Academy.
超过75年,我们为 反社会与情绪困扰
For over 75 years we have served adolescents
的青少年 服务,他们面临的是
who because of social and-or emotional challenges that they face
无法在传统的 学校环境 成长
have been unable to thrive in a traditional academic environment.
我们学校 提供大学的 技能培训教育
At Sword and Cross we combine college preparatory education
先进的临床技能
cutting edge clinical services
与 多样的武术课程 专注于
and diverse enrichment programs that focus on
人格的成长
personal growth.
这次 你要把他关在哪里?
Where do you want him this time?
过去那里
Through there.
我马上过来
I'll be right with you.
包括
Including
剑术, 游泳
fencing, swimming
和使用我们世界闻名的 Valor 图书馆
and the use of our world renowned Fowler Library.
我们 创建者的理念是 基于 核心原哲....
Our founder's philosophy is based upon the core principles...
现在 交出危险物品. -危险物品?
- Now dump your hazards.- Hazards?
酒,毒品,任何一种武器
Alcohol. Drugs. Weapons of any type.
与帮派有关的东西 或衣服
Gang related items or clothing.
音乐拨放器,平板电脑,电玩,笔记型电脑
Music players, tablets,gaming systems, laptops.
手机
Cell phones.
不,不,不,我需要手机
No, no, no, I need my phone.
你每周有 使用电话10分钟 的权限
You get ten minutes of phone privileges once a week.
你在开玩笑吧? -这是什么?
- You're kidding.- What's this?
我不知道,它是一个礼物...危险物品
- I don't know, it's a present...- Hazard.
我不能整天待在这里,Randy
Haven't got all day, Randy.
我马上过去.Arriane
I'll be right there. Arriane!
你能带 Lucinda(露西) 去她的宿舍吗?
Could you show Lucinda to the dorms?
当然可以,交给我吧
Sure, I got it.
你可以在午餐后 来拿你的袋子
You can pick your bag up after lunch.
告诉我 你的周末,卡恩(Cam),我要洗耳恭听一下
So tell me about your weekend, Cam.I'm all ears.
- Arriane.亚利安
- Luce.露西
我们会严格管控他
We're going to keep him on a very short leash.
没有必要起诉他 这次,比尔
There's no need to press charges this time, Bill.
你知道我们已经 隐蔽这事
You know we've got this covered.
我们会 看紧这家伙的
We'll keep a good eye on him.
你要远离 Cam 这家伙.  是的,为什么?
- You're going to want to stay away from Cam.- Yeah, why's that?
他是个 问题人物
He's trouble.
非善类
Not the good kind.
让我看看你的 课表
Let me see your schedule.
很好,你跟我们同班
Good, you're with us.
我们? 先修班
- Us? - Prep-track.
我们喜欢 一起修课
We tend to stick together.
这里大部分的孩子是 精神问题 转来的
Most kids here are psych referrals.
他们很幸运过了一天 没有弄湿自己
They're lucky to get through the day without wetting themselves
或是攻击老师,因为他们的铅笔没削均匀
or attacking a teacher because their pencils are unevenly sharpened.
不要吓到了,学校把他们隔开 住宿
Don't be spooked, though.They keep them separate.
所有严重心理缺陷的 住在三楼
All the serious mental defectives are up on the third floor.
这里是一个 大 疯人院
It's one big pharmapalooza.
这是我房间,208号
This is me. 208.
你住哪里?
Where are you?
313号房
你在耍我,对吗?
You're messing with me, right?
你是一个...(精神病患)
You're a psy...
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉
Sorry.
告诉我 有关你的幻觉.你称它什么来着?
Tell me about your hallucinations.What do you call them?
影子幽魂
Shadows.
什么时候开始的?
And they started when?
当时我还小的时候
When I was little.
5或6岁.我记得正确时间.
Five or six. I can't remember exactly.
你还会 看见他们吗?
And you still see them?
没有，有段时间　没看见了
No. I haven't for a while.
告诉我,露西
Tell me, Lucinda.
你想 为什么你会在这里?
Why do you think you're here
剑与十字 学院
at Sword and Cross?
问问 法官
Ask the judge.
我看过你的档案,我知道 法官的想法
I've read your file.I know what the judge thinks.
我不了解的是 你的决定
What I don't understand is your decision.
医生 Seagulls说 你的药物治疗 非常稳定
Doctor Segal says that on medication, you're stable.
没有幻觉 没有妄想症 没有恶梦
No hallucinations.No paranoia. No nightmares.
我没有发疯 你知道的
I'm not crazy, you know.
没有人说 你疯了
No. Nobody's saying you're crazy.
每个人都说 我疯了
Everybody's saying that.
你了解吗? 如果你吃 处方签药物,你就可以离开这里
Do you understand, that if you take your prescribed medication you can leave.
回家.回去你的学校
Go home. Go back to your old school.
与你的朋友 在一起
Be with your friends.
我不喜欢 他们看我的感觉
I don't like the way they make me feel.
如果你拒绝 服药,你就必须待在 这里
But if you refuse, you need to be here
在一个法院裁决的 治疗设施中,受到监控
in a court sanctioned treatment facility, under supervision.
即使是 被锁住(与世界隔离)
Even if it means being locked up
我宁愿做我自己 而不是为了配合 而 假装成某人
I'd rather be me than pretend to be something I'm not just to fit in.
你有机会去过正常的生活
You have a chance at a normal life.
可怜的家伙,她不知道 她为什出现在这里
Poor thing.She has no idea what she's in for.
也许 这次(轮回)不一样.你知道一些 我不..?
- Maybe it'll be different this time.- You know something I don't..
有点改变 也不错
It'd just be nice for a change, that's all.
好吧 让我们把这事 变得有趣些
Alright, let's make it interesting.
20 比 1,露西会死在火里,跟过去一样
Twenty to one Luce goes down in flames, just like always.
我押100
I'm in for a hundred.
- Arriane!
- What?不行吗?
- Gabbe?- It's cruel. This isn't a game, Roland.
Gabbe呢? 这太残忍了. 这不是一个游戏.Roland.
也许 它是游戏(上帝与 Lucifer的游戏)
Maybe it is.
好戏又要 上演了
Here we go again.
心灵 是自己的 归宿,而且心灵
The mind is its own place and itself
可以使 地狱 变成 天堂
can make a Hell of Heaven.
这是什么?
What's that?
弥尔顿 著作的 失乐园
Milton. Paradise Lost.
你是 露辛达(露西) -是的
- You're Lucinda Price?- Yeah.
我是 苏菲亚 .你是我宗教哲学课程的学生
I'm Miss Sophia.You're in my Philosophy of Religion class.
你是来拿书的吗?
- Did you come for your books?- Mm-hmm.
高中数学,英国文学,化学,宗教与历史
Pre-calc, English lit, Chemistry,Religion and History.
Oh,还少了一样
Oh, still missing one.
你介意吗? 它在 特别收藏区 那儿
Would you mind? It's in special collections.
好的
Sure.
很高兴见到你 露西
Ah, it's a pleasure to meet you, Luce.
谢谢
Thanks.
Hi.
嘿,等等
Hey, wait.
你掉了这个 (丹尼尔没说话 就走了)
You dropped this.
可恶
Shit!
你吓到我了
You scared me.
好吧
Alright.
你 这可怜的家伙
You poor thing.
天呀,你跌倒了吗?
- Jeez.- Oh, did you fall?
有受伤吗?
Are you hurt?
我很好.  不,你不好
- I'm fine.- No, you're not.
你从来没好过,你的存在 令人讨厌
You've never been less fine in your whole nauseating existence.
到这里 是一个 坏的选择
Coming here was a bad choice.
听着,如果我有令你不愉快,我向你道歉
Listen, if I did something to upset you, I'm sorry...
你让我恶心
You make me sick.
你什么都不是
You're nothing.
你眨眨睫毛,甩甩头发,期待世界 会停止运转吗?
You bat your lashes and flick your hair and expect the whole world to come to a stop.
你跟本不认识我
You don't even know me.
我知道 你是杀人的 小精神病
I know you're a murdering little psycho.
嘿,分开
Hey! Break it up!
精神病溅货! 你应该 贴着 你警告标签 来
Psycho bitch.You should come with a warning label.
还真快(你刚到学校)
That was quick.
是她 找你麻烦的,是吗?
- She...- Don't tell me she started it.
我想 应该是的
I'm sure she did.
但是 你可以不必走入 她的圈套
But that doesn't mean you have to take the bait.
你说的对, 我很抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
打架 可以被 开除
Fighting is grounds for expulsion.
对你而言 会被转到州立 精神病院
Which for you would mean a transfer to the state psych hospital.
那是 你想要的吗?
Is that what you want?
不是
No.
今天是你第一天到学校,我想你一定还没有 读到 管理条例
Since today is your first day and I'm guessing you've yet to read the code of conduct
我罚你打扫 庭院
I'll just give you yard duty.
你呢? 你跟我来
And you? You come with me.
你知道 没有允许 你不可以来这儿
You know you're not supposed to be in here without a pass.
我只是..
I just, ah...
Oh,不,不,不,开玩笑的
Oh, no, no, no, that was a joke.
我很抱歉
- Oh.- I'm sorry.
Oh,天呀
Oh, gosh.
不搞笑吗?
Oh. Not funny?
今天真是个很烂的第一天
It's just been a really rough first day.
是呀 ,欢迎来到 剑与十字 学院
Yeah. Welcome to Sword and Cross.
这个地方 令人发疯
- This place is...- Crazy.
我是Pennyweather Van Syckle-Lockwood.你可以叫我 Penn(佩恩)
I'm Pennyweather Van Syckle-Lockwood.You can call me Penn.
好的
Okay.
你是 Lucinda Price,但是每个人叫 你 Luce(露西)
And you are Lucinda Price,but everyone calls you Luce.
由 Dover 转学到这儿,高中成绩 GPA 4.2分
Transferred here from Dover with a 4.2.
令人钦佩
Impressive.
你怎么知道的?
How did you know that?
该死. 我像狗仔队吗
Shoot. Was that stalkery?
是的,有一点
A little bit, yeah.
抱歉
Sorry.
实际上,这里是一个很小 很小的学校.
See the thing is, this is a really small school. Like really, really small.
无限的小,这里发生的事不多
Like infinitesimally small,and not a lot happens here.
不像 Dover, 你是新来的女孩 既聪明又漂亮
It's not like Dover, and you're the new girl and you're smart and you're pretty
所以,我猜你会是 正负两方
so I'm guessing that you're going to be the centre of a lot of attention
注意的焦点
both positive and negative.
很好
Great.
告诉你吧
Tell you what.
我要走了,让你做你的事
I'm gonna go, let you do your thing
也许你想原谅我,你可以
and then maybe if you're feeling forgiving, you can...
忘记我在洗手间向你搭讪,给你太多的知讯
forget the whole me accosting you in the bathroom with too much information
而你只想清静一下,而我胡言乱语一堆
when you just want to be alone and then rambling on and on
因为 我也不知道如何 阻止我自己
because I don't know how to stop myself
说出刚发生的学校状况,请再给我一次机会 好吗?
from talking situation that's happening right now and give me another chance?
现在 我要走了
I'll go now.
- Hey, Penn? 嘿,佩恩
- Yeah?什么事
你可以告诉我 如何回到宿舍吗?我有点迷路了
Do you mind showing me back to the dorms? I'm a little bit lost.
当然可以
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
万一 现在真有天使 在我们之间 在地球上
What if angels actually walked among us right now, here on earth?
那就是 坠落天使 的故事
That's the story of The Fallen.
天使 被逐出天堂
Angels cast out of heaven
会被定罪 过着凡人的生活
condemned to live their lives alongside us mere mortals.
会被放逐,是因为他们 没有选边站
Banished, because they failed to pick a side
在大天使 Lucifer对抗天堂 的战争中
in Lucifer's war against Heaven.
谁可以告诉我,天堂发生怎样战争?
Who can tell me what the war in Heaven was about?
陶德
Todd?
善良对抗邪恶吗?
Good versus evil?
不是,你回答的太单纯了
No, that's too simplistic.
大天使 Lucifer是上帝最爱的天使
Lucifer was God's favourite.
是上帝最亮的光
His brightest light.
是什么事情,使他背叛上帝呢?
What caused him to turn from God?
有谁知道?
Anyone?
因为他的女朋友 甩了他
'Cause his girlfriend dumped him.
其他的天使 发生了什么事呢?
What happened to the other angels?
那些支持撒旦的 被放逐到地狱去
Those that sided with Satan were banished to Hell.
只有忠诚的天使 留在天堂
Only the faithful remained in heaven.
没有做出选择的天使,被放逐出天堂
The angels that didn't choose,they were cast out.
他们是 坠落天使
They are the Fallen.
被迫在人间 工作
Forced to walk the earth
有些坠落天使 仍保有 天使的本性
some of the Fallen retained their angelic nature
忏悔并等待机会 重新返回天堂
repented and wait for the chance to return to Heaven.
其他与 Lucifer结盟的天使
Others aligned themselves with Lucifer
过着 找寻欢乐,恶作剧与混乱 的日子
finding pleasure in mischief and chaos.
但是没有一个群组 可以离开这个世界
But neither group can leave this world
因为 他们之中的一个
because of one of their own.
叛逆天使(本片中的男主角 丹尼尔)
The rebel angel.
他拒绝选择 战争中两边的 任何一边
He rejected both sides of the war
上帝 与 Lucifer(大天使)一样
God and Lucifer alike
都在追求人类的 爱
all in his pursuit of human love.
其他的坠落天使
The other fallen angels
必须持续 待在人间
must remain here on earth
直到他(叛逆天使)选择 战争进行中的一边
until he chooses a side in the only war that has ever been waged.
这场战争至今还在 肆虐着 我们
The war we still see every day raging all around us.
这事,你们在 主日学 学过一些吧?
But surely you learned some of this in Sunday school?
没有,在我成长过程 不曾去过教会
No, I didn't go to church growing up.
真的吗?
Really?
是的,我父母没有宗教信仰
Yeah, my parents aren't really religious.
所以..你不曾受洗
So, you were never baptized?
是的 ,我没受洗
Um, no.
战争 是不是应该结束了呢?
Is it supposed to be over, the war?
我意思是,就神学观点来看
I mean, theologically speaking
如果恶魔还活着
if the Devil is still alive
还有谁能阻止他 再挑起战争呢?
What's to stop him trying from trying again?
非常好的问题
Excellent question.
So,还有谁要下注?
So, any more takers on that bet?
是的,让好戏继续滚下去,Roland.
- Yep. - Keep them rolling, Roland.
露西, 你这可怜的家伙
Luce, you poor thing.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
这里发生了什么事?有人受伤吗?
What is going on here? Is anyone hurt?
没有,我真的没事
No, really, I'm fine.
这里的食物很好
The food is fine.
任何东西?   -任何东西,甜心
- Anything ? Anything, sweetheart.
-
那一定会是 你的橘子肉桂煎饼 加上生奶油 与香蕉
Definitely your orange cinnamon pancakes with whipped cream with bananas.
- That sounds...听起来..
- Hey!  嘿
什么事奖这么久? 快点
What's taking so long? Come on.
我要用电话
I need it.
妈?妈?
Mom? Mom?
分配的时间到了.分配的时间到了
Allocated time completed. Allocated time completed.
我真不敢相信 我必须等一星期 才跟我父母 通电话
I just can't believe I have to wait a whole week to talk to them.
你知道吗 我连 说 再见 的机会都没有
You know, I didn't even get a chance to say goodbye.
你可以用 我周二的配给时间
You can have my time on Tuesday.
不. -可以的,我不会用到它
- No.- Yeah, I'm not gonna use it.
我已经待在这 6年了.每个我认识的人
I've been here six years.Everyone I know is here
以及 每个有兴趣与我聊天的人 就在这房间里
and everyone I'm interested in talking to is in this room.
那你父母亲呢?
What about your parents?
我不是故意要问
I've been meaning to ask.
(佩恩:) 我怎么会在这里?
How I ended up here?
你不必 告诉我.那没有什么 大不了的
You don't have to tell me.It's not a big deal.
好吧 我父母离婚后
Well, after my parents got divorced
他们俩个 都不要我,所以
neither of them really wanted me around so
他们决定 寄宿学校 会对我最有益
they decided that boarding school was in my best interest.
一旦我母亲看见那本 宣传小册子
And as soon as my Mom saw that brochure
上面有 孩子们骑马 与 游泳 等等
the one with the kids riding horses and swimming and stuff
就这样.找寻结束了.我就入学到这里
that was it. The search was over,I was enrolled and here I am.
所以,你不是有窃盗前科,躁郁症,厌食症自裁者.
So you're not a kleptomaniac,manic depressive, anorexic cutter?
不是
No.
我的诊断 比那些 更糟
My diagnosis is much worse
我想我是 无药可救了
and, I'm afraid, untreatable.
我有 TDP.
I have TDP.
心律不整 吗?
TDP?
悲剧地被父母丢弃
Tragically Disinterested Parents.
是的,我父母真烂
Yeah, my parents suck.
但是 这里有个池塘(很快乐,如鱼得水)
But there's a pool.
是呀.这里是很适合我
Yes,there is a pool.
你一定是在 开玩笑
You've gotta be kidding me.
我不敢相信
Don't tell me.
Cam 恋爱了?
Is Cam in love?
那会让你 把事情弄得更困难
That could make things difficult for you.
别忘了 你在替谁工作
Just don't forget who you work for.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
我昨天还没有机会 对你说声谢谢
I didn't get a chance to say thanks yesterday.
不必客气
Don't mention it.
总之 还是要谢谢你
Well, thank you anyway.
还有一件事 我有点尴尬要问你
There's one more thing I'm a little embarrassed to even ask but...
那就 不要问
Well, then don't.
但我 坚决要弄清楚它
Well, I've committed now.I'm just going to go for it.
你似乎 好眼熟
It's just you seem really familiar to me.
好像我在哪里 认识过你
Like I know you from somewhere.
有可能吗?不,不可能
- Is that possible?- No.
如果是,我会记得你
I'd remember you.
因为我仍然在想....
Because I keep thinking that...
我必须走了 再见
I've gotta go, alright? I'll see you later.
谢谢你
Thank you.
Hey,新来的女孩.前面几天,事故很多吧
Hey, new girl.Pretty eventful first few days.
已经计划好逃离 这儿了吗?
Already planning your escape?
是呀,正在考虑
Yeah, considering it.
要来点 早餐吗?
You ah, you want some breakfast?
的确 很诱人,但是,我上课快迟到了
That's tempting, but I'm actually running late to class.
迟到总比不到好
It's better never than late.
真好喝
This is really good.
这是 从哪里 弄来的
Where's it from?
我从 工厂休息室 偷来的
I stole it from the faculty lounge.
他们有一台 意式浓缩咖啡机
They have a pretty decent espresso machine.
你真是不可救药(习性难改)
You're incorrigible.
他们 都这样说我
That's what they tell me.
你不同意吗?
You don't agree?
我只知道 我喜欢什么
I just know what I like.
你不在意 会犯 校规吗?
And you don't mind breaking the rules to get it.
Well...
如果有奖励,冒险是值得的
if the risk is worth the reward
我认为 有何不可
I don't see why not.
你认为呢?
What about you?
你不会待在  剑与十字学院 就坚决遵守校规
You don't end up at Sword and Cross by following the rules.
你不觉得 你有一点叛逆吗 ?
You got a little rebel in you?
我只是被误解了(我不 叛逆)
I'm just misunderstood.
不,我看得出来
No, I see it.
你很漂亮(像天上星星一样闪亮)
You got a spark.
你的意思是什么?
What do you mean?
意思是.你是那种 宁愿做对的事,不愿做 被要求做 的人
Means you're the kind of person who'd rather do what's right than what you're told.
意思是 你是麻烦人物
It means you're trouble.
你认为 你了解我 哈?
You think you know me, huh?
我知道 我喜欢什么.
I know what I like.
时间到了
Time's up.
Roland 这星期五要举辨一个派对
Roland's having a party this Friday.
是非正式的
- Yeah?- It's just casual.
你可以带你的朋友来. 好的
- You can bring a friend.- Okay.
我们一伙人在周末都会聚在一起,舒缓一下压力
Bunch of us get together at the end of the week to blow off some steam.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不进来上课吗?
Aren't you in this class?
Oh,这课 我以前全都听过了
Oh, I've heard it all before.
准备 ,开始
En garde! Allez!
他们怎么也玩这个？
How well did they think this through?
你知道 提供武器给药物治疗中的青少年
You know, giving weapons to heavily medicated teenagers
来控制愤怒 是很危险的吗
with poor impulse control and anger issues.
停
Halt!
好了,更换 伙伴,巴克,你练习结束了
Alright, change partners. Sparks, you're up.
露西,让我们看看 你有没有注意 听课
Price, let's see if you've been paying attention.
有记住 我刚才的示范吗?
Remember what I showed you?
不全然记得
Not really.
准备
En garde!
开始
Allez!
不是很糟嘛
That wasn't terrible
对一个 第一次练剑的人来说
considering it was just your first time.
好了
Alright.
交换伙伴
Switch partners.
丹尼尔,到这边来
Grigori. Come on over.
准备
En garde!
开始
Allez!
非常好
Very good.
再来一次.准备
One more. En garde.
开始
Allez!
丹尼尔 停下来
Grigori, halt.
Halt!停下来
你们两个 停下来
Both of you, halt!
我给他一星期
I give it a week.
有关受洗的事?会影响她吗?
What about the whole baptism thing?Could that affect her?
细节无关
The details don't matter.
丹尼尔　每次都过度迷恋她 但结果都一样
Grigori always finds something to obsess over but it never makes a difference.
现在 你只要放松心情 就好,并 接受 露西的死亡
Now you all just need to relax and accept that Luce is gonna die
而且 你，丹尼尔或 Sophia老师 也都无法阻止
and there's nothing you or Daniel or Miss Sophia can do to stop it.
我以为 你从来没有 击剑过
I thought you'd never done this before?
我没有 学过
I haven't.
我身体 接管了一切
My body just took over.
好像 我确切地知道 我该怎么击剑
Like I knew exactly what to do.
Huh.
真诡异,你曾经 有这样的经历吗?
It was weird. Have you ever felt that?
有的,像似 我学 三角学的时候
Yeah, I was kinda like that with trigonometry.
开始,所有过程依序出现在我脑海, 我觉得我是天才
It all just fell into place so at first I was like 'wow, I'm a genius.'
后来 我才记得 我们去年就学过了,一点都不 令人讶异
But then I remembered that we covered it last year so I guess that's not as impressive.
你陷进去了(暗恋), 对吧
You got it bad, huh?
不,不是那样
No, it's not like that.
好吧, 也许是的
Well, maybe it is.
只是 我对 Daniel有这种感觉
It's just I have these feelings about Daniel.
好像 我认识他
Like I know him.
好像我认识他 很久很久了
Like I've known him for a really long time.
是呀, 也许你们一起上过幼稚园之类的
Yeah, maybe you guys went to preschool together or something.
我问过他 是否我们有见过,他说 没有
Well, I asked him if we'd met before and he said no
而且,基本上 他一直躲我 ,很奇怪
and he basically ran away. It was strange.
是吗
Yeah.
的确有点 不太对劲
Something definitely not quite right... hmm.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
不要告诉任何人 我将告诉你的话,否则我会有很多麻烦 ,好吗?
I can get in a lot of trouble if you tell anybody what I'm about to say to you, okay?
我不会告诉任何人
I won't.
我自愿在 空闲时间待在办公室打工,虽然听起来很烂
So I volunteer in the office for my free period which I know sounds totally lame
但事实上很酷 很有趣,电脑有怪异的通路
but is actually kind of cool and fun in its own weird way, sort of.
结果 我发现 Randy 根本不会用电脑
Turns out Randy is totally useless when it comes to computers.
他竟然 问我最基本的电脑技能,诸如
So he asks yours truly to do the most basic tasks like
在他桌上电脑找档案,收寻打喷嚏刺猬之类的影片
find files on his desktop and search for videos of sneezing hedgehogs or whatever.
有趣的是
Meaning
我完全进入学校每个人的档案纪录
I have full access to everybody's academic records.
我看到 丹尼尔的档案
I've looked at Daniel's file.
完全是空的
It's empty.
他没有 住家地址,没有紧急连络人, 什么都没有
He's got no home address,no emergency contact, nothing.
这件好看吗?  - 好看
- Do you like this? - Yeah.
他和所有的那些孩子一样
It's the same with all those kids.
他们这群人 都有点怪怪的
There's just something not quite right about that whole group.
你 不曾听过他们谈论到他们的家庭 或是之前就读的学校
You never hear them talk about their families or their old schools.
他们很少去上课,但他们却像 以前就相互认识
They barely ever go to class and it's like they all knew each other from before.
等等,你是指 谁?
Wait, who do you mean?
丹尼尔先来
Daniel arrived first.
他去年初转学到这里,然后是Gabbe
He transferred at the beginning of last year and then Gabbe.
高高金发,常常与丹尼尔在一起的 那个女生吗?
The tall blonde that's always hanging around him?
是的 那个果糖甜度 85度 的女生
Yep, 85 percent confectionary sugar by volume.
然后是 Arriane
Then Arriane.
Oh,是的,我来的第一天,她带我参观学校
Oh, yeah, she showed me around my first day.
然后 Molly,"智障"的女生
And Molly. Serious defective.
然后是 Roland,我完全不知道 他是怎么通过 每周的小考
And Roland, I have literally no idea how he passes his weekly pee test
然后是 25岁的未来先生,Cam,他去年春天转学到这里
and then Mr. Future 25 Years to Life,Cam, transferred in last spring.
Sophia老师也是.
Miss Sophia, too.
她今年刚到,她不理会任何人 除了她最喜欢的事物
She's new this year and totally ignores everyone except her favourites.
这事你怎么看? 问倒我啦.
- Well, what do you make of it? - Beats me.
我真不敢相信. 什么事?
- I can't believe it. - What?
我要去参加一个Roland的派对
I'm actually going to one of Roland's parties.
oh,你们两个看起来 真可爱
Oh, don't you two look lovely?
谢谢
Thanks.
你也是, 一如往常
You do too. As always.
你看起来 好甜美
Aren't you sweet.
我有点讨厌她 是不是不对呀?
Is it wrong that I kind of hate her?
为什么,因为她完美无瑕,有蜂蜜的香味,阳光的肌肤,
Why, because she's a flawless,honey-scented, spray tanned,
傲美的身材,金发碧眼带着笑容
bikini waxed manicured blond-fembot who's always smiling
而且正在亲吻你暗恋的对象?
and is at this moment kissing your crush?
是的,几乎就是这样
Yeah, pretty much that.
你也许错了,但是 我完全可以理解
It might be wrong, but I totally get it.
有人要喝酒吗?
Anybody order drinks?
我想知道 你怎么会要来这派对
I'm still trying to figure out how you ended up here.
是你邀请我的,记得吗?
Well, you invited me, remember.
那不是我的意思
That's not what I meant.
显然是要加入我们,对吗?
With the rest of us it's obvious, right?
吸毒
Drugs.
恶意破坏
Vandalism.
沮丧
Depression.
花痴
Nymphomania.
为什么 你要来这样的地方呢?
So why did you end up at a place like this?
也许,我不是看起来那么纯洁
Maybe I'm not as innocent as I look.
- Hello.
- Hi.
那是 飞行莲花夹克 吗?
Is that a Flying Lotus jacket?
是的
Yeah.
你真是个 颓废派成员
You are such a hipster.
我意思是 好的那一方面(世面灵通的人)
In... in a good way, I mean.
我知道 你不是故意装酷 才穿的
Like you know,it's not like you're trying to be cool.
但是 你穿起来 的确很酷
Like you're actually cool.
Wow.
我这一生,被指控好多罪行.
I've been accused of a lot of things in my life
但从不装酷
but never that.
- Hey.嘿
- Oh, hey. Thank you.谢谢你
Oh,这是给我的吗?
Oh, is that for me?
好棒,还有饮料呀.谢谢,
Amazing. Thank you so much. Thank you.
不客气
Sure.
Um...
So...
这是表演会吗? 或是...
Is it from a show, or...?
是呀.很棒的现场秀.
Yeah. He's amazing live.
我看过他跟Teebs 在加州 艾西维尔市
I saw him in Asheville with Teebs.
少来.Teebs 是我最喜欢的 后迪拉 艺人
Get out of it. Teebs is my favourite post-Dilla artist.
雷猫科技 改变了我的生活
Well, Thundercat changed my life.
不,也许除了雷猫科技,还有别的
Well, no, except maybe for Thundercat.
你有听过 Daylight混音吗?
Have you heard the Daylight remix?
那个男低音
That bass.
完全正确
Exactly.
好也
Yes.
想到 不好的回忆吗?
Bad memories?
所以 你还在想念他?
So do you still think about him?
谁?
Who?
你杀掉的男孩,Trevor
The boy you killed. Trevor.
你知道的,高高的 有着迷人眼睛的 那个男孩.
You know, tall, easy on the eyes.
至少,他过去 常和你约会
Well, at least he was before he hooked up with you.
现在 你都忘光啦
Now he's not so much to look at.
你怎么会知道 他
How do you know about him?
我知道你很多事,疯子露西.  -离我远一点
- I know a lot about you, Crazy Luce.- Get that away from me.
我打赌 我知道的 比你自己 还多
I'll bet I know you better than you know yourself.
对不喜欢火的人来说,火 似乎特别喜欢你
For someone who doesn't like fire,it sure does seem to like you.
够了
That's enough!
闭嘴 Arrian,让我在你脸上留个疤痕来匹配你背上的疤
Shut up, Arri, let me give you a scar on your face to match the one on your back.
退下,Molly
Back off, Molly.
- Are you okay? 你还好吗?
- Yeah, I'm fine.我没事
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我只是玩弄一下 你的神经病女友
Just having some fun with your psycho girlfriend.
给我离露西 远点
Stay away from Luce.
你听到了吗?
You hear me?
Oh,你忘记自己是谁啦.Cam
Oh, you've lost track, Cam.
你一直想要 你得不到的
You always want what you can't have.
这次,她是我的
This time she's mine.
放开我
Lay off me!
外太空 绝对有生物存在
There's definitely life in outer space!
嘿!露西 在哪里
Hey! Where's Luce?
我不知道,我以为 她跟你在一起
Um, I don't know.I thought that she was with you.
好吧
Okay.
她不需要你的帮忙.  -那么,谁来保护她呢? 你吗?
- She doesn't need your kind of help.- Who's gonna protect her, you?
放轻松点,你们这些多情鸟,这是派对时间
You know, you lovebirds need to relax, huh? It's a party.
我突然感觉很累
You know, I'm feeling pretty tired all of a sudden, actually.
我想我必须回去了
I think I'm just gonna go.
你要我陪你走回去吗?
You want me to walk with you?
不,没关系,你留在这 好了
No, it's okay. You should stay.
Hello?
Molly.
Molly,拜托.我知道是你
Molly, come on. I know it's you.
Trevor 在哪里?
Where's Trevor?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉.  -你做了什么,你这个 怪胎
- I'm so sorry. - What did you do, you freak!
都是我的错
It's my fault.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
告诉我,在剑与十字学院 ,第一个星期 过得如何?
So tell me, how was your first week at Sword and Cross?
很好
Fine.
没有事件要报告?
No incidents to report?
幻觉,恶梦 呢?
Visions? Nightmares?
没有
No.
你的影子幽魂呢?
What about your shadows?
很好
Good.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没事.
Nothing.
我只是无法 置之不理.   -什么?
- I just can't get past it.- What?
我觉得 我认识你
This feeling that I know you.
我们不是以前 谈论过这事了吗?
Haven't we been through this?
是的,但是
Yeah, but...
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
你我之间有关连
There is something between us.
而且 你也感觉到了,对吗?
And you feel it too, don't you?
好吧
Alright. Okay.
你是对的, 我应该告诉你实话
You're right.I should have just told you the truth.
It's...
我了解 我曾经对你很热情,而且...
Like I realise I haven't been very warm towards you, and...
你真是个 浑球
You've been a real dick.
是的,但请相信我,不是因为 你曾经做过什么事
Yeah, but believe me. You've got to know it's not because of anything you've done.
有个女孩...
See, there's this girl...
Gabbe 吗?
Gabbe?
什么? 不是
What? No.
不是 Gabbe,是另外一个女孩
No, not Gabbe. No, just someone else. Another girl.
我猜 你会说我不再跟她一起,但是
I guess you could say I'm not with her anymore, but
我还 爱着她
I still love her.
我想说的是 ...
What I'm trying to say is...
你是一个烂摊子,我最好离你远一点?
You're a mess and I'm better off without you?
似乎就是这样
Something like that.
事情没那么简单
It's not that simple.
你大可以说出你的感受
You can't tell someone how to feel.
是的
Yeah.
我希望 事情发展不是这样
I wish things could be different.
嘿.不要走
Hey! Don't go.
原来你在这里.我正担心你呢
There you are. I was worried about you.
你离开派对 忘了说再见
You left the party without saying goodbye.
发生了什么事??
What's wrong?
露西 停下来 跟我说话
Luce? Stop! Talk to me!
我与 Molly 有一段有趣的对话 昨晚
I had an interesting conversation with Molly last night.
OK. -她知道我的事
- Okay. - She knew things about me.
这些事 我从来没与他人分享过.  -然后呢
- Things I haven't shared with anyone.- And...
有人把事情告诉了她
Someone's been talking to her.
这个人看过我的档案
Someone who's read my file.
Oh.对的,你的怀疑 很有道理
Oh, right, 'cause that makes perfect sense.
我背叛了你的信任 成为一个无情的,没灵魂,又缺乏想像力的霸凌者
I betrayed your trust to a ruthless,soulless, unimaginative bully
与不卫生 和很烂的说话技巧 的Molly交换,为的是什么?
with suspect hygiene and poor language skills in exchange for what?
为了两个身体穿洞(耳洞)与囚犯刺青吗?
Oh, two free body piercings and a prison tattoo.
我相信我能侥幸成功 但你抓到我了
I was sure I'd get away with it,but you caught me.
好吧,至少 你已长大 足以承认这事
Well, at least you're big enough to admit it.
到底是怎么了? 说真的.
What's wrong? Really.
你有看过我的档案,对吗
You have read my file, haven't you?
当然
Of course.
所以你知道有关...
So then you know about...
影子幽魂 的事?
the shadows?
你还有看到 它们吗?是的
- Do you still see them?- Yeah.
你 现在 有看到吗?
Do you see them right now?
没有,但是 自从我来到这里,我的幻觉 变得更糟了
No. But since I've been here they've gotten a lot worse.
我很害怕,我怕有人会受到伤害
And I'm scared. I'm scared somebody's going to get hurt.
不,别傻了   -我没有
- No, don't be ridiculous.- I'm not.
死去的 Trevor 当时就站在那里
Trevor was just standing there.
他就站在那里 而且我们..  -好吧,详细地告诉我 发生了什么事
- He was just standing there and we...- Okay. Tell me exactly what happened.
Trevor 举止像似 我整年不在
Trevor acted like I didn't exist all year
然后 突然在派对上对我调情
and then suddenly at this party he was flirting with me.
来吧 跟我去 小屋里
Come up to the cabin with me.
正当我要感到
Just one time I wanted to feel
正常(亲热)
normal.
你要喝点酒吗?  -好呀
- You want a drink? - Sure.
你有听到吗?
Did you hear that?
Trevor 你确定 只有我们吗?
Trevor, are you sure that we're alone?
露西
Luce.
放轻松
Relax.
不
No.
停.停.离开,离开
Stop. Stop. Get off. Get off!
倒底是 怎么了? -请离开这里
- What the hell? - Please, get out of here.
发生什么 事?
What's going on?
不.不!
No. No!
露西?
Luce?
影子幽魂 比过去 更大
The shadows were bigger than ever.
然后, 突然 所有的东西都付之一炬
And then suddenly everything exploded.
我不知道我是怎么逃到外面的 而 Trevor 没有逃出来
And I don't know how but I was outside and Trevor didn't make it.
Trevor!
Trevor 在哪里? 告诉我
Where's Trevor? Tell me.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉.   -你做了什么,你这个 怪胎
- I'm so sorry.- What did you do, you freak?
那是我的错. 我很抱歉
It's my fault. I'm so sorry.
Trevor!
他死了 因为我有问题(精神问题)
And he's dead because there's something wrong with me.
我很高兴你愿意做我的朋友
And I'm really glad you want to be my friend
但是 你应该远离我 因为我很危险
but you should stay away from me because I'm dangerous.
你想要 他死吗?
Did you want him to die?
不想,你想伤害他吗?
- No.- Did you try to hurt him?
不想 -那么,那不是你的错
- No.- Well, then it's not your fault.
你不必孤单一人,你需要一个朋友
You don't need to be alone, Luce.You need a friend.
让我来帮助你
Let me help you.
为什么?
Why?
因为 那就是朋友 该做的事
Because that's what friends do.
上次 我们讨论到 因为大天使Lucifer的自大 让他坠落
Last time we were discussing how it was Lucifer's pride that led to the fall.
是的
Yes.
因此 谁可以翻译一下?
So who can translate?
Humilitas homines sanctis[拉丁文.]
angelis similes facit[拉丁文.]
et superbia ex angelis demones facit.[拉丁文.]
有人 能翻译它 吗?
Anyone?
自大让天使变成魔鬼
It was pride that turned angels into devils.
那是什么,露西?
What was that, Luce?
谦卑使人变成天使
It is humility that makes men as angels.
自大让天使变成魔鬼
It was pride that turned angels into devils.
我们有 拉丁文学者 在我们当中
We have a Latin scholar in our midst.
不, 我不曾
No, I've never...
我只是猜的
It was just a guess.
那么 这与 叛逆天使(本片中的 丹尼尔) 有什么关系呢?
So how does that relate to the rebel angel?
是因为 他的的自大,固执地追求 爱情 超过上帝
Wasn't it his pride, his stubborn pursuit of love over God
让他成为坠落天使 陷在人间吗?
that led to the Fallen being trapped on earth?
Arriane?
我已经厌倦去听 你扭曲这个宗教寓言 用以套在你自己的信仰上
I'm tired of listening to you twist these religious fables to fit your own beliefs.
你说过这个故事 , 爱情是选择的关键
You tell this story of yours as is love was a choice.
我不喜欢你说话的语气
I don't care for your tone.
也许你只是生气  叛逆天使选错了 女孩
Maybe you're just pissed the rebel angel chose the wrong girl.
出去
Get out.
我很乐意
Gladly.
我宁愿在地狱永远地被火烧烤
I'd rather burn in hell for all eternity
也不愿意再花一秒钟 听你一大堆胡说八道
than have to listen to one more second of your pious self-satisfied ravings.
刚才 真精彩
That was kind of awesome.
是呀.你想 她会被留级吗?
Yeah. Do you think she'll get suspended?
我猜 即使她被留级 .那些孩子一点也不会在乎
I doubt she even gets detention.Those kids get away with everything.
嘿.我忘了我的毛衣. 我待会儿赶上来
Hey, I forgot my sweater.I'll catch up with you guys.
好的
Okay.
听我说 你一定要注意 Cam
Listen to me. You've got to keep your eye on Cam.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我不认为雕像倒下是一个意外事件.她(露西)正处于危险中
I don't believe the statue was an accident. She's in danger.
就在意外发生前,我看见他(Cam)在顶楼
I saw him on the upper floor just before it happened.
他为何要那么做?
Why would he do that?
你也听到了.露西还没有受洗
You heard. She isn't baptized.
露西 需要我们的保护，她...
She needs our protection. She's...
抱歉, 我只是忘了我的毛衣
Sorry, I just... I forgot my sweater.
我去跟她说
I'll go talk to her.
嘿.露西
Hey, Luce!
等等
Wait.
什么事? 你要干嘛? -没事
- What? What do you want? - Nothing.
我想也许 我们可以一起走走,散散步
I just thought maybe we could walk together.
Oh.
当然可以
Sure.
你今天 在教室 画什么呀?
What were you working on in class today?
没什么, 是一个...
Nothing. It's ah...
一种 绘画本小说
sort of a graphic novel.
是什么样的故事呢?
What kind of story?
我想,你可以称它 是一个浪漫爱情故事
I guess you could call it a romance.
故事有个 快乐的结局吗?  -我不知道
- Does it have a happy ending?- I don't know.
你不知道 故事的结局?  -不,还不知道
- You don't know how it ends? - No, not yet.
老实说,我有点卡住了
I'm sort of stuck, to be honest.
让我听听 告诉我你写的故事
Well, let's hear it. Tell me your story.
不.我不认为 那是个好主意
No. No, I don't think that's a good idea.
不好吗?
No?
也许,我可以帮你 完成故事的结局
Maybe I could help you with the ending.
好吧
Okay.
故事是有关一个男孩和女孩
It's about this boy and this girl
他们彼此非常相爱
and they love each other more than anything
但是, 他们绝对不可以在一起
but they can never be together.
为什么? -因为有一个诅咒
- Why? - Because there's this curse.
每17年他们相遇
Every seventeen years they meet
而且 开始相恋
and they fall in love
正当他们最幸福快乐的时候,那女孩就会死掉
and then just when they're happiest, the girl dies.
所以,故事是个 悲剧?
So it's a tragedy?
那男孩 怎么办呢?
What happens to the boy?
他等待
He waits.
他不会变老 也不会改变 面貌
He doesn't age or change.
他继续谈恋爱
He remains in love.
多年过后 最终 女孩又再回来
Years pass, and eventually she returns.
同一个女孩吗?
The same girl?
女孩 变了
She's changed.
她有新的名子,新的家人
She has a new name, new family.
她不记得他
She has no memory of him
但是他知道 她就是那个女孩
but he knows it's her.
是她的灵魂
It's her soul
转世再生
reincarnated.
然后 他们又再相恋一次
And they fall in love.
一直都是这样
Always.
我意思是,每一次转世有一点点不一样
I mean, each time it's slightly different.
虽然有无限次的轮回与相逢, 最后结果都一样(女孩会死)
There are infinite versions but the end is always the same.
但是,结尾 都是一个 亲吻
But then all it takes is a kiss
然后 女孩就死了
and she's gone.
是谁下的诅咒 在他们身上的呢?
Who put the curse on them?
是魔鬼 他本人
It was the devil himself.
他忌妒他们的爱情,因此 他想拆散他们
He was jealous of their love,so he tried to break it.
一定有 他们能解决的方法,对吗?
There has to be something they can do, right?
他全都试过了
He's tried everything.
他试着 找她
He tries looking for her
试着 躲避 她
then tries to avoid her.
试着逃离 无法避免的 心碎
Tries to run away from the inevitable heartbreak.
但是诅咒 总是赢家
But the curse always finds a way,no matter what.
故事中的女孩
The girl in your story.
她就是你 在游泳池提到的 那一个吗?
Is she the one you mentioned at the pool?
他还爱着她 的那个女孩?
The girl you're still in love with?
她 是故事的灵感来源,是的.
She's the inspiration, yeah.
是这个女孩吗?
This girl?
好吧 你逮到我了. 那是
Alright, you got me. It's um...
我用你做为 故事中女孩的化身
I was using you for her current incarnation.
这背景应该是在 巴黎
This is meant to be Paris.
1723年
In 1723.
这想法 真笨
It's stupid.
为什么 是我?
Why me?
因为你很漂亮
Because you're beautiful.
但是 我画错 眼睛了
But I messed up the eyes.
在你的眼睛里 总是有点神秘
There's always been something about your eyes.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
告诉我这个地方.你曾经待过那里吗?
Tell me about this place.Have you been there before?
那有关系吗?
Does it matter?
- Yes.是的.
- Why?为什么?
过去 我从来没有旅行过
I've never travelled before.
我甚至 不曾离开过这个国家
I've never even left the country.
但我知道 有一家咖啡店 就在画中右上方
But I know that there's a cafe just off to the right
而且我也知道 下雨过后 那里闻起来 像是茉莉花香
and I know it smells like jasmine after it rains.
我也知道 经营那家咖啡馆的老人,总是饥饿不饱,而且对她太太很残暴无情
And I know that the old man that runs the cafe is kind to his dog and he's cruel to his wife
我知道这些事情,因为我过去,曾经在那里待过
and I know these things because I've been there.
而且是 我跟你一起在那里
And I've been there with you.
哦,露西  拜托
Oh, Luce, come on.
不要
Don't.
不要告诉我 我疯了
Don't tell me that I'm crazy.
露西,那只是一张画,好吗?
Luce, it's a drawing, alright?
它只是一个故事,就这样
It's a story, that's all.
你在说谎
You're lying.
我希望我能告诉你 你想要听的
I wish I could tell you what you want to hear.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
吹蜡烛
Blow.
生日快乐,露西
Happy birthday, Luce.
你怎么知道 我生日?
How'd you know?
你要 许个愿望吗?
Did you make a wish?
我不能告诉你 否则愿望不会实现
I can't tell you. It won't come true.
Oh,那没关系
Oh, that's okay.
我已经知道 你的愿望是什么
I already know what you wished for.
是吗?
Oh, yeah?
我的愿望是什么?
What'd I wish for?
是答案
Answers.
你想要真相
You want the truth.
晚上8点在 拱门见,我将告诉你 所有的事情
Meet me at the arches at eight and I'll tell you everything.
露西
And Luce?
穿漂亮一点
Wear something nice.
晚上是 派对时间
It's party time.
17岁生日快乐,妈妈 和 爸爸
Happy 17th Love Mom and Dad
看看你
Look at you.
Oh, wow.
那是你吗?
Is it yours?
为了今晚
For tonight.
这机车 你怎么弄到的?
How'd you manage that?
那是Rolland的特殊才华
It's Roland's special talent.
他能替你 弄到任何你想要的东西
Anything you want, he can get it for you.
我会感到遗憾吗?
Am I going to regret this?
只有一个方法可以知道
There's only one way to find out.
上车.-门都没有,我来骑车
- Come on.- No way, I drive.
你真的要 今晚一开始 就被一个女孩拒绝吗
You really want to start the night by saying no to the girl?
好吧
Okay.
我跟你在这里做什么呢?
What am I doing here with you?
庆祝
Celebrating.
这点 你很在行
You're good at that.
每次我问你问题
Every time I ask you a question
你都有 很机灵的方法 来 躲开回答
you have some clever way of avoiding the answer.
才不是这样
That's not true.
举例来说..你在哪里长大的呢?
Here's an example. Where did you grow up?
看吧?
See?
你为什么不告诉我 任何有关你的事呢
How come you won't tell me anything about yourself?
因为 我正在享受美好时光 ,我不想毁坏它
Because I'm having a nice time and I don't want to ruin it.
毁坏美好时光 不好,huh
It's that bad, huh?
我比较喜欢 这个
I prefer this.
你承诺要告诉我 答案
You promised answers.
来吧, 露西. 今天是你的生日
Come on, Luce. It's your birthday.
我想 有些其他的东西 是你想要的
I'm thinking there's something else you might want.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
停止!我告诉过你 离她远一点
- Stop!- I told you to stay away from her.
丹尼尔,你在做什么?
Daniel, what are you doing?
为什么? 因为你很在乎她吗? -停下来
- Why, because you care so much about her?- Stop it!
不要吵了.  -不,因为我知道你想干什么
- Stop!- No, because I know what you're capable of.
你仍然与 Lucifer在一起,承认吧
You're still with Lucifer. Admit it!
为什么你不告诉她,丹尼尔?告诉她所有的事
Why don't you tell her, Daniel?Tell her everything.
她要知道真相.  -不要吵了 你们两个
- She wants the truth.- Stop it!
给我离她 远点,  -你没有权利 把事情说出来
- Just stay away from her!- You don't have a say in it.
我不知道 这是怎么回事,但是 它全都与我无关
I don't know what's going on here but it has nothing to do with me.
我从不相信 我命中注定要与某个人在一起
I never bought into that idea that there's one person you're meant to be with
但是 我的幻象是如此的真实 而且 我的感觉是如此真实
but my visions are so real and my feelings are so real
它像是 前世今生之类的,我也不知道为什么
it's like past lives or something.I don't know.
然而 每件事都与 丹尼尔有关,但他总是把我推开
And everything's connected to Daniel somehow but he keeps pushing me away.
而且 Cam 也隐瞒了些事情
And Cam's hiding something too.
你认为呢? 佩恩
So what do you think?
我认为你是个 浑球 没有告诉我 那天是你的生日
I think you're a jerk for not telling me it was your birthday
但是我宁愿忽视它 因为它太荒谬 可笑了
but I'm willing to overlook that because this is so ridiculously juicy.
你相信 转世 轮回 再生 吗?
Do you believe in reincarnation?
不,一点都不相信
No. Not at all.
我也不相信 ,但是
I didn't think so either but
这些事件,一定有个解释
there has to be some sort of explanation for this.
Hmm.
也许我能帮助你
Maybe I can help.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我们只需要再多做一件事
We just need one more thing.
什么?
What?
你怎么知道 那是 Todd 的房间?
How do you know which room Todd's in?
它是怎么 工作的??
So how does this work exactly?
你有看过年刊相片吗?
Have you got those yearbook photos?
Todd曾经在非常酷的 脸部辨认运算法系统 工作过
Todd's been working on this really cool facial recognition algorithm.
那不全都是我写的程式
It's not all my code.
它是由Carnegie Mellon公司开发出来的
It was developed at Carnegie Mellon,
但是 我做了一点 修改与调整
but I've tweaked it a little.
他太谦虚了
He's so modest.
抱歉
Sorry.
这也许需要一分钟
This might take a minute.
它正在收寻
It's just searching.
露西? Hello?
Luce? Hello?
我们找到 相配的了
We've got hits.
Whoa.
看看这些名子
Look at the names.
他们一定是亲属关系
they must be relatives.
Oh, what?什么
这...怎么会..
The actual... Fuck.
把它印出来
Print it.
我去拿(佩恩说)
I'll get it.
Todd,我指望你有点解释
Todd, I'm counting on you having some sort of explanation
因为我真的在这相片中
because I am really struggling here.
我也不知道 这是怎么回事
I haven't got the faintest idea.
我爱你
I love you.
让我们看看 还能找到些什么
Let's see what else we can find.
它又发生了..
It's happening again.
不
No.
离我远点(露西 喊叫)
Leave me alone!
露西?一切都还好吗?
Luce? Everything okay?
Luce?露西
Penn!(陶德 叫喊)
我去找 Penn佩恩(陶德说)
I've gotta find Penn!
Penn!佩恩
佩恩 你在哪里?
Penn, where are you?
陶德!
Todd!
我必须找到 佩恩
I've gotta find Penn!
- No!
- Penn!佩恩
Todd!陶德
No!
在我们学校医务室这里
Here at the school infirmary
我们可以提供 与医院相同的 照顾
we provide the same care she'd receive at the hospital.
我要带她回家
I want to take her home.
医生说得很清楚.她现在的状况需要 临床观察
The doctor's clear. She needs to remain under clinical supervision.
要多久？ -直到她稳定
- For how long?- Until she's stable.
你应该休息一下
You should get some rest.
我会打电话到旅馆叫你,一旦露西可以接见访客
We'll call you at the hotel as soon as Luce is able to receive visitors.
这里 没有我们能做的了
There was nothing we could have done.
我拒绝接受 这事实
I refuse to accept that.
我本来可以警告她的. 我可以在那里...
I could have warned her.I could have been there...
那样会有帮助吗? -事情过了,没有关系了,好吗?
- When has that ever helped? - It doesn't matter, okay?
她需要我们,而我们让她失望
She needs us and we let her down.
这是个犯罪案件调查吗? 目前不是
- Is this a criminal investigation? - Not at the moment.
火灾是因为 闪电 引起的.那是初步的报告
The fire was caused by lightning.That report is preliminary.
这案子与 Trevor Beckman的案子 很类似
Given the similarity to the Trevor Beckman case
我们一定要询问她
we'll definitely want to question her.
我不允许你跟她说话 在没有律师的陪同下
I don't want you talking to her without her attorney present.
我们今天聚在这里
We come together today
来吊念 我们失去的亲爱的朋友(Todd),他是如此的仁慈大方
to mourn the loss of a dear friend,a kind and generous...
他(Todd)的生命是如此短暂
whose life was far too brief to mourn the loss...
悲剧的发生让我们十分震惊
whose tragic passing comes as a shock to us all.
我们会永远记得 这位仁慈 又大方的朋友
We will always remember a kind and generous friend
他的陪伴总是 带给我们欢乐
someone whose company was always a pleasure
虽然今天 我们可以理解地要克服悲痛
and although today we are understandably overcome with grief
我要求你们要有信心
I ask you to have faith that in time
我们的伤痛将化为力量
our pain will prove strengthening
而这个最后的遗愿
and ultimately a testament
是陶德在乎的
to how much Todd mattered
而且直到永远
and always will.
他不仅仅是个慈爱的孩子
Not only was he a loving son
而且是仁慈又大方的朋友
but he was also a kind and generous friend.
我们必须把我们的悲伤 传换成 某种力量
We must transform our sadness into something strengthening.
这就是 我们如何纪念他的生命的方式
That's how we celebrate his life
与 确保他的遗愿
and ensure his legacy.
你在他被杀后 才出现在他的葬礼吗?
You show up to his funeral after you get him killed?
我知道 这是你干的
I know you're the one doing this.
你在胡说什么?
What are you talking about?
雕像坠落 ,图书馆起火
The statue. The fire in the library.
你试图要杀露西
You were trying to kill her.
杀死露西,是你该做的事,丹尼尔
Killing Luce is your thing, Daniel.
你竟敢....
Don't you dare...
你是怎么了,丹尼尔? 你害怕 来点竞争吗?
What's the matter, Daniel? You afraid of a little competition?
我对露西的爱意 是真的
What I feel for Luce is real.
她这次不一样了.她应该得到 比 你可以给她的 更多
She's different this time. She deserves more than you can give her.
如果 你再接近她...你想干嘛?
- If you come near her...- You'll what?
你要看她死去 多少遍呢?
How many times do you have to watch her die?
我爱你
I love you.
Luce!露西
Oh, Penn!佩恩
陶德呢?
Todd?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的抱歉,都是我的错
I'm so, so sorry. It's my fault.
不要这么说
Oh, don't say that.
是真的.那影子幽魂是完全同一个
It's true. The shadows were exactly the same.
它是完全同一个...别说了. 好吗?
- It was the exact same...- Stop it, okay?
不是你 造成的
You did not cause this.
我不要再听到它
I won't hear it.
好吗
Okay.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你许愿了吗?
Did you make a wish?
前世 与 命中注定
Past lives and destinies.
你要真相
You want the truth.
她一点都不认识我.只要一个亲吻.
She doesn't know me at all.All it takes is a kiss.
但是 他知道 就是她
But he knows it's her.
露西,不
Luce! No!
你亲吻他,你就会死
Kiss him and you'll die.
是谁对他们下的诅咒?
Who put the curse on them?
是恶魔 他本人.  -丹尼尔,不
- It was the devil himself.- Daniel, no!
露西,不要
Luce, no.
你会死的
You will die.
你好点了吗?
You feeling better?
我全身都疼,但是 我还活着
Every part of me hurts, but I'm alive.
那很好
Well, that's something.
我记得
I remember.
什么事? 所有的事
- What? - Everything.
火灾
The fire.
你抱着我
You carrying me.
在你手臂中 感觉像是我们...-Well,你很可笑 荒谬
- Being in your arms, it felt like we were...- Well, you were delirious.
也许是
Maybe.
但是,我不只 记得这些
But that's not all I remember.
我还记得 这张照片
I remember this.
我记得 我们一起照相 的日期
I remember the day this was taken.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
够了
Enough!
我知道 我是谁
I know what I know.
我这一生 人们都说我疯了
My whole life people have told me that I'm crazy.
露西,  -让我们看看 他们是否 正确
- Luce.- Let's see if they're right.
不,露西 从那里下来
No, Luce, get down from there.
不,露西
No, Luce.
不!
No!
一直都是你,露西
It will always be you, Luce.
从过去到现在,一直都是 你
Just as it always has been.
现在 不是多愁善感的时刻了
Now is not the time for sentimentality.
露西吗?
Luce?
这项链 是 我给你的
I gave you this.
已经 很久 很久了
It was a long time ago.
这怎么可能?
How is this possible?
没有关系. 不,每次坏事
- It's okay.- No, every bad thing
要发生在我身上 都是因为这东西
that's ever happened to me is because of that.
不,他们部会伤害你.他们只是观察
No, they can't hurt you. They just observe.
那火灾.他们杀了 Travor.
The fires. They killed Trevor.
露西.影子幽灵 不会造成火灾,也不是 你放的火
Luce, the shadows didn't cause the fire and neither did you.
它们叫做 Anocess
They're called Announcers.
看
Look.
把它们想成一道 可以看到过去的窗户
Think of them as windows into the past.
他们追踪你生命中最重要的时刻
They're attracted to the most important moments in your life.
我看到的是什么?
What am I seeing?
我们在一起的生活
Our lives together.
我们已经相爱 数千年了
We've been in love for thousands of years.
露西 所有你的 幻觉都是真的
Luce, all your visions are real.
所以 我们是一直在 转世 轮回吗?
So we're reincarnated?
只有你是
You are.
我是..
I'm...
一个天使
An angel.
我是 坠落天使之一
I'm one of the Fallen.
停止
Stop!
不要 吻他,露西
Don't do it, Luce.
你吻他 你就会死
Kiss him and you will die.
这就是为什么 我一直试着躲开你,但是 我又不能
This is why I tried so hard to push you away but I can't.
你没有告诉她吗?(接吻 与 死亡)
You didn't tell her?
我非常抱歉 -真不可思议,
- I'm so sorry.- Unbelievable. You're unbelievable.
什么? 我不了解,为什么?
What? I don't understand, why?
诅咒是我的惩罚,为了不让我选边站(Lucifer 或上帝)
The curse is my punishment for not taking a side at the Fall.
露西 不要听信 他所说的
Luce, don't listen to him.
待在我身边 露西 ,我选择了你
Stay, Luce. I chose you.
我选择 爱情
I chose love.
不要听信 他所说的,露西
Don't listen to him, Luce.
如果 你吻他 你就会死
If you kiss him, you will die.
我已经看过 数千遍了.   -不,这次不一样
- I've seen it a thousand times.- No, this time it's different.
我保证 这次不一样
I promise it is different.
他是个骗子 露西
He's a liar, Luce.
(Cam:) 如果你与我再一起,我可以保护你
If you stay with me, I can protect you.
(丹尼尔:) 你已经看过 我真正的形式
You've seen me in my true form.
这次不一样
This is different.
我可以保护你
I can protect you.
这会是 我们厮守 在一起的机会
This could be our chance.
请听我的
Please.
露西,我可以给你 一个未来
Luce, I can offer you a future.
一个生命
A life.
我不能再一次 失去你
I can't lose you again.
我知道 我想要的
I know what I want.
不
No!
我还活着
I'm still here.
你相信 你已经打败 诅咒吗?
You think you've beaten the curse?
你不知道 她(露西)正处于是多么的危险之中
You have no idea how much danger she's in.
大天使 Lucifer知道 她 还没有受洗
Lucifer knows she's not baptized.
我不了解 告诉我为什么?
I don't understand. Tell me why.
他(丹尼尔) 为自己解除的诅咒 不是为你解除诅咒
He lifted the curse for himself, not for you.
Lucifer 会来找她 现在
He'll come for her now.
丹尼尔 不能保护你, 露西
Daniel can't protect you, Luce.
我能
I can!
她跟我在一起 才会安全
She's safer with me!
事情有自然法则,丹尼尔
There's a natural order to things, Daniel.
你不可以 随你高兴 就这样做
You can't just do as you please.
转世 轮回的循环 已经被打破了
Well, the cycle's been broken.
Roland! Molly!
Luce!
你跟我一起来
You're coming with me!
保护她的安全,我需要跟 Cam 把事情做个了断
Keep her safe. I need to deal with Cam.
不论我带露西去哪里,我不要 Cam 跟随
Where I'm taking her,I don't want him to follow.
他会把 Lucifer 带来找我们
He'll lead Lucifer right to us.
他们都是天使
They're all angels.
我不会让你 把露西带去给Lucifer
I won't let you take her to Lucifer!
我不再 听信Lucifer了. -你骗人
I don't answer to him anymore.  -Liar.
你把露西陷入 危险的那个人, 丹尼尔
You're the one putting her in danger, Daniel.
不要假装 你在乎 她的安危
Don't pretend you even care about her!
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
我可以保护她
I can protect her.
离她 远一点
Stay away from her!
这是怎么回事?
What the heck!
回到你们的房间 把门关上
Back to your rooms. Shut the door!
这是一级防范
This is a lockdown.
等待 事情结束
Wait for the all clear.
这是一级防范,把门关上
It's a lockdown. Shut the door.
不要害怕.   -我不害怕
- Don't be afraid.- I'm not.
我不是你的敌人
I'm not your enemy.
我没有要杀 露西
I'm not trying to kill her.
那么是谁?
Then who?
露西 等等
Luce! Wait!
图书馆火灾 是她放的火.她...
She set the fire in the library. She...
佩恩
Penn?
不
No!
去吧
Go!
露西 你的时间到了,我已经厌倦了 等待
Luce, your time has come.I am tired of waiting.
结束吧 现在
This ends now.
你每一次出现 就阻断 丹尼尔 返回天堂的意愿
Every breath you take keeps Daniel from his rightful place in heaven!
丹尼尔! -你才是真正的 诅咒
- Daniel!- You are the real curse.
露西
Luce!
Sophia, what have you done?
Sophia,你做了什么事?
你宣称上帝的仆人
You claim to be a servant of God.
我是.战争正在进行中
I am. There's a war going on.
忠诚的士兵 该做 他们必须做的事
Loyal soldiers do what they must.
包括谋杀吗?
Including murder?
你拒绝为 大局着想
You refuse to see the bigger picture.
你一直 都是这样
You always have.
她死了 你将不得不 选择 哪一方(Lucifer 或 上帝)
With her gone you'd have been forced to choose a side
而且 秩序将会恢复
and order would have been restored.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我不了解为什么她要这样做
I don't understand why she'd do that.
她是一个 盲信入迷的人
She's a fanatic, Luce.
她替上帝做战 但是,她太过头了
She fights for god, but she went too far.
为什么 她要杀死 佩恩?
Why would Sophia kill Penn?
她为什么要杀我呢?
Why did she try to kill me?
你还没有受洗.如果你死了,你将永远不会进入轮回
You're not baptized.If you die, it'll be forever.
Sophia 认为你死了(永不轮回), 我就没有理由留在人间
Sophia thought with you gone I'd have no reason to stay on earth
然后我会返回天堂
and I'd return to heaven.
但是 Cam 是正确的
But Cam was right.
Lucifer 会来找你
Lucifer will be coming for you.
那就是为什么 我必须带你去一个安全的地方
Which is why I need to get you somewhere safe.
我知道一个地方 ,我有朋友在那儿,他们会保护我们
I know a place. I have friends there.They'll protect us.
我们必须走了
We have to go.
我们现在不能离开,我不能让 Penn 留在这里
I can't leave now. I can't leave Penn.
我们会照顾她
We'll take care of her.
佩恩
Penn!
她将会跟我们一起去.走吧.
She'll come with us. Go. Please.
露西
Luce.
他们会带 佩恩 一起来
They'll take Penn with them.
快没有时间了,我们必须走了
There's no more time. We have to go.
等一下,听我说
Wait a minute. Listen.
我一生都在寻找真相
My whole life I've been searching for the truth.
我一直想知道 我到底是谁
I've been trying to figure out who I am.
为什么,我从来无法溶入我应有的生活
Why I never seem to fit in to the life that was supposed to be mine.
现在,我好害怕
And now I'm terrified.
我有 比过去更多的疑问
I have more questions than I ever have before
这就是原因
but... this is it.
这就是我
This is who I am.
这就是 我心的依归
This is where I belong.
在这里 跟你在一起
Right here, with you.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道这些 从我第一次看见你
I've known it from the first moment I saw you.
我爱的 将一直是你,露西
It will always be you, Luce.
永远
Forever.
谢谢欣赏
翻译.校稿:Robert Chou
结局: 叛逆天使 丹尼尔 打破了 Lucifer的诅咒
他选择了爱情 也选择 上帝那一边
所有 坠落天使 也都可以 重返天堂
后记:
Lucifer　后来因为战败被打落地狱，成了地狱七君王之一，魔名为 撒旦